Iginari Explorers!
I'm Kitami Rine and this is Yasumori Waka!
Today we are the two members of the Iginari Expedition!
Today, we have an important project!
We have an important project for you today.
Important? It's always important.
Don't get carried away.
Well, today's exploration is...
Let's announce Jasfest!
Important!
Here it comes! It's that time of year again!
Jasfest is going to be held again this year, and today we are going to make a big announcement about it!
Ta-da!
Here it is!
Everyone is wearing jerseys! Jasfest will be held on Sunday, October 27th at the special rooftop stage on the 10th floor of EWINS!
Yay!
As I just said, what a surprise!
If you don't wear your jersey, if you don't wear your jass, you won't be allowed to enter!
Everyone must wear Jass, but you can wear the jersey you used to wear in middle school or high school,
You can wear the jersey you wore in junior high school or high school, or you can wear a slightly more casual jersey that looks like you might step on it through the whole thing, like Garfi's.
We will be selling JASMO on the day of the event! So it's happening again this year?
Jasmo, Jarrah, Jarrah, Jarrah!
How to put it out! That's so magomaniacal!
It's nice, it's got the end chain mark and E-BEANS on the chest.
I like it.
I have an endorsement, too.
And this year's performers are
Tomoku Iitani!
Thank you every year!
And Rian!
Nanami!
Why am I watching this?
It's not a home video.
Mr. Amefurashi!
Why are they all watching it?
Yes, are you watching?
And Ebidan Sendai.
Wave! Wave!
Same office, I guess.
I noticed there were a lot of little boys in there that I didn't know.
Little boys you don't know?
And the next thing you know, it's nice to meet them all.
I'm looking forward to it.
And Satoshi Ogata!
You look strong!
What do you mean, strong?
You seem really determined.
Did you have her do some kind of stretch time last year?
Do a forward bend for Ms. Satoshi Ogata.
Oh!
Oh, yes, last year... we did a fitness test.
It wasn't weak, it was great.
But Kitami-san set a new record.
Maybe I'll get a channel.
Subscribers!
Yes! He's coming again this year!
And Kimitaka and Himori will be there too!
Yes, they will be there as MCs!
We are sure that this year's event will be just as exciting as this one, so please come out and join us!
Yes! Please come!
And speaking of JASFACE, of course we will have live performances,
But what else we do every year is to have a physical fitness test corner!
That's right!
We do it every year. As Kitami-san mentioned earlier about bending forward...
We will have the physical fitness test again this year. Let's go to the stage on the 10th floor and rehearse the physical fitness test.
I'd like to rehearse the physical fitness test. It's been a year since you both did it last year.
You are still young, but there is a possibility that your physical strength may be deteriorating. If we check your fitness here, there is a possibility that you may be able to get back on track by the time of the show.
I'd like to move to the 10th floor.
Let's go.
Let's go for it!
Now we're moving to the 10th floor.
Revision.
Great.
Okay, let's get right to the first event.
The first event is
Grip strength test
We do this every year.
In my image...
The annual physical fitness test at Jaspers.
I have an image that the two of us are performing at a very high level.
Yes, they are.
Might be much stronger.
Let's give it a try.
I looked it up, and the national average grip strength for a girl in her 20s
29.
That's the national average.
Let's give it a try.
I'll do my best.
Go for it.
You should speak up.
It'll go better.
That's right.
Like the hammer throw.
Koji Murobushi makes a lot of noise.
The moment he throws.
What should I use?
Something Korean?
Ready?
Adieu adieu!
I feel like a freak.
There's a weirdo in there.
Don't ever put any effort into that voice.
Okay.
What's the result?
What?
It's the hardest one... and it resets while I'm trying to figure out what to do with it.
I can't take it anymore. I wonder if we'll ever see it again.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait! The police are coming!
What? It's buggy.
It's buggy.
24.6.
That was a little higher.
Last year.
Oh, my God, I'm surprised.
So you're just below the national average for girls?
Does that mean they're weaker?
Definitely not.
Next...
You must be Yasumori.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Okay.
Okay, this type.
I'll announce it.
35.8.
Wow!
Can I try one more time?
Thirty-five?
It's got to be over 30.
Wait a minute.
Can I do it even if you don't speak, Lynn?
You're the tense type.
I'll take Kitami-san's tense pattern.
Great, great, great!
Okay.
How's that?
Twenty-eight.
Wow! Almost average!
I wonder if I can get it out.
I had a bad memory of grip strength in middle school.
You know those physical fitness tests in high school or early high school?
When we didn't all get along yet.
We'd do it in order of surgery number.
The girl in front of me said
She said, "Okay, you're next.
I said, "Thank you.
The girl in front of me said she'd take my measurements.
So I said, "Hmph.
That was pretty high, too. 30 something paces.
What? Like, "What?
I remember being really scared.
I had to suppress my grip strength.
But now, thanks to Jasfest
I've been able to clearly show you what I'm capable of.
I'm glad.
My classmates have been using honorifics ever since.
Mr. Yasumori
Korilla world
That's me.
So it was kind of nice.
No, it's great.
It's cool, on the contrary
I'm sorry
Let's go to the next event.
Yes, sir.
Inoki.
Abdominal Muscle Measurement
This is not a part of Jaspers' physical fitness test.
Today, we don't have a lot of equipment, so we can't do it.
So instead of that...
How many times can you do sit-ups in 30 seconds?
This is the national average.
For girls in their 20s, it's like 19.96.
About 20.
You two do sit-ups, too, don't you?
Why are you doing it?
Why don't you answer me, why don't you just show me the two of you and your poses?
Pull, pull, pull.
Well, I don't even know if I can do it for another 30 seconds.
30 more seconds and I might not make it.
Why have you been acting so vulnerable all day?
It's okay. It's okay.
You're a manly man.
You're handsome.
You're so handsome.
Okay, let's do this.
Okay.
Let's start with you, Kitami.
Okay. How do we do this?
I've prepared a mat for you to lie on.
First of all, you have to press down...
What do you do with your hands?
I thought it was like this.
It's like Xavier. Your hands are like Xavier's, and this is for 30 seconds.
Count it. I'll count the seconds.
Go for it!
Okay, let's go!
Kitomi-san's sit-ups!
Go for it!
You're fast!
Good, good.
Ten seconds.
I'm trying.
15 seconds. We're halfway there.
He's talking.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Finished. Wow, we made it to the end.
We'll announce the results!
The results are in!
Hama-chan?
Kitami-san made it 24 times!
Oh! That's great!
4 or 5 times higher than the average.
How was it? Kitami-san was a little rough around the edges.
I had time to spare.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Impossible! You can't do anything with that kind of editing.
You're awesome! I could have done it.
I had time to spare?
The last 5 seconds or so were pretty bad.
But it's great! It's way above average!
That's what I'm talking about.
But you've got a lot more stamina than when I was a student.
What? You're still young. I didn't have a mother when I was a student.
It's only a few years.
Shut up. You want to do it?
For my son.
Let's go, Yasumori-san. Looks amazing, Yasumori-san.
I'll have to tell him you're mad, too.
Let's go when you're ready.
Ahhh...
No, it's not a nap.
It's not an ahhh.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going to measure your abs, Yasumori-san.
Yes, sir.
All right, let's start!
Whoa, isn't he silently apneic?
Yes, sir.
Are you okay? Breathe?
Ten seconds!
Oh, my God!
Great, great, great, great!
Twenty seconds!
Oh, my God!
Five.
Four.
Three.
One.
That's it!
Maybe!
27!
No, I was counting!
You were counting?
You're so generous!
27! Almost one every second!
Isn't that amazing?
Isn't it amazing?
Did you try it?
No, but it was surprisingly easy.
What is it with you two? You make it seem like you can handle it.
Well, I'm only 21.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Age wise...
Twenty-two.
Oh, no!
I'm the same...!
Five months is a big difference.
No, I'd understand if you were in elementary school.
But 24 times around.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, she's looking up at you, Princess.
No, no, no.
It can't be 28 times.
It can't be 28 times because she looked up at you.
Twenty-eight times.
That's too sweet.
No, but...
No, it's great.
And sit-ups.
We both beat the national average.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Dancers.
Repeat the horizontal jump.
Wow, I'm starting to get tired.
That's only two repetitions.
This is the third one.
How many repetitions can you do in 20 seconds?
National average.
44 in 20 seconds for a girl in her 20s.
That's pretty good.
I'll measure it.
Okay.
Yasumori, please count.
On.
Then, please do your best for 20 seconds.
Do your best.
Why did you come out?
Okay, are you ready? I'm ready.
Kitami-san's challenge... 20 seconds of horizontal jump.
Ready, start
Relay step.
All right.
Ten seconds.
5 seconds.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
There you go.
Come on.
No, don't act like you rushed in, you were right there.
Kitami Irie-san!
Kitami, you're wearing it.
I'm sorry.
Kitami Irie's result?
You're not good at this.
Perspective is good.
The result was 52.
Wow!
That's wonderful!
That's an average with room to spare.
What kind of handshake is that?
Good job, sir.
Hey.
No, it wasn't a ledger meeting.
It was that comfortable.
Plenty of room?
Wow.
What's with the stunt? Manual?
It's like a wind-up.
That's great, 52.
That's what I'm talking about.
What's up?
It was fun.
It's okay... we'll just have to do it manually.
That's what I'm talking about.
And this one cleared the average.
Oh, no!
Let's go, Mr. Asamori!
I'll do my best.
Kitami-san, please count.
OK.
You both like cameras?
I'm not saying, "Good luck.
I can't see you.
What's that?
Oh, my God.
Okay, you ready?
Yes.
Let's see how Yasumori-san's horizontal jump measures up.
Okay, let's start!
Careful getting up.
10 seconds.
Go as hard as you can!
GO!
Four, three, two, one, there you go!
There you go. - All right.
The result.
46!
Forty-six!
Huh?
Hey! Hey!
I got a flat tire.
Where are you going? !
I panned.
I'm going crazy.
I'm having a hard time.
I'm totally fine.
But I'm above average.
The next one's the last one.
What?
Maybe he's not done yet.
Isn't it over?
Next up is a little trial run.
I'm thinking of doing it for the first time at JASFES this year.
I just had two people try it today.
If I think it's going to be a lot of fun...
I'll give it a try.
I see.
The final event will be a quick jass suit change.
It's not a physical fitness test, it's a showdown.
Well, as I mentioned in the opening, there's this year's Jass Fest Jass, right?
I have a set of them here, one at a time.
There's this one, right?
Mr. Kitami versus Mr. Yasumori.
Let's start preparing.
Who's going to be the first to cut the top and bottom?
Who can cut the top and bottom
to cut the top and bottom.
When you're done changing
Raise your hands and say "Jass.
Jass!
Start sitting on the floor.
Seiza first.
Lady Jass!
Stand up.
You can start from the top or the bottom, whichever you prefer.
When you're done changing, jus' jus' jus'!
You have to say Uno.
You have to say "jass", not "yes".
What if I forget?
Forget what?
If you forget to say jass...
Oh! What if you realize you forgot to say it?
If one of you jassed in the meantime, you'd win.
Out of the blue.
Okay, rules?
Who's the fastest king?
The first queen of the fastest change of clothes is...
Rie Kitahi and Waka Yasubori.
Who will win?
Let's go!
Here we go! Ready!
Jass!
Here we go.
Yasumori-san finishes putting on his underwear from the bottom.
Is Ms. Kigami having trouble with the top zipper?
Meanwhile, Yasumori-san is only left with the zipper.
All right! Jass!
It's decided!
The future queen
Rie Kitami
What's this?
What is it?
What is it? I don't know whether to be happy or not.
I'm sorry to hear that, Yasumori-san.
Yes, my first dentist.
I've been working hard for a year.
Yes, well, I put everything I had into this day, but...
Well, I couldn't get the trophy.
I would like to do my best again for the next year so that I can change my clothes as soon as possible.
I'm looking forward to next year's challenge!
Thank you very much.
I'm going to run around in the mountains...
Let's run over.
What's with the outfit?
Who is this guy who can wait so long?
I'll do it, Jas.
Boo-boo, it's not tied up... it's an adjustment...
Oh, no!
You too!
This is the most popular scarf of the season.
You're wearing it around your pants, too, right?
That's why they're so popular this season.
If you wear that, you'll have to bring two Jas.
I know what I'm going to look like, but...
It's a very specific face.
How do you do that face?
That's why it's called the Jass fan grand prix.
The way you dress.
Is this possible?
This is good, too. The judging panel is headed by Ogatori-san.
Really?
He's the one who decides the venue.
This is a good way to dress.
Can I make one last announcement?
Yes! So, October 27th, Jasfest.
We've just had our fitness test.
And of course, there will be live performances.
So please wear your Jas!
We are going to enjoy the autumn sports season together!
We're looking forward to seeing you there.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, it's like Resident Evil.